# Ken Suzuki

# **BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER | WEB DEVELOPER**

Ken Suzuki is a fullstack and blockchain developer with over 9 years of experience, managing all aspects of the development process.

As a senior developer, he has in-depth knowledge of many areas and possesses the ability to code quickly and efficiently. He's passionate about solving challenging problems that others find difficult or impossible. He's ready for an opportunity to use his skills to grow your revenue exponentially. He enjoy learning new technologies and sharing findings with my colleague.

- Always Open to Remote Job
- 6+ years of experience in Web Development

Experience in React/Redux development/Tawilwind CSS more than 5 years.

Composed front-end app structure & built React components and UI from given mockup.

Good TypeScript programming skills in VueJS and ReactJS.

Good knowledge of Functional Programing, Object-Oriented Programming and design patterns.

React | React Native | Redux | Vue | Angular | Node | Typescript | Next | Nuxt | MongoDB | Tailwind CSS | Storybook

- 3+ years of experience in Blockchain Development

Experience with Solidity, web3.js, ethers.js, Immutable X, Hardhat with a strong understanding of the EVM.

Design, develop, program, test, debug, maintain smart contracts code.

Build governance systems with multi-stage voting.

Worked on many DeFi and Dapps based on Ethereum Blockchain and have enough experience in developing and writing Smart Contracts.

Expert in Uniswap, Sushiswap, Swapping tokens, Staking, Yield Farming, Lottery Smart Contracts etc.

Evaluate and evolve scalability, security, performance, and gas optimization.

Solidity | Ether.js | Web3.js | Rust | Hardhat

✓ mnteristo@gmail.com

• 5-11 Nashiharachō, Nara, 630-8253, Japan

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ken-suzuki-4b7a6022a

### **SKILLS**

REACT.JS SOLIDITY PYTHON

VUE.JS RUST SMART CONTRACT

WEB3.JS SOLANA TRUFFLE ETHER.JS CHAINLINK HARDHAT

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### SENIOR BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

HYFI Corp Feb 2022 - Present

- Built NFT lottery smart contract architecture and smart contract by using ERC1155
- Get trustable token price and random number for lottery by using chainlink
- Implemented Web3 integration and frontend development
- Implemented proxy contract for upgradable and signature for security

Technologies: Solidity, chainlink, Web 3.0, Dapps, Moralis

#### SENIOR BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Grayblock Jul 2021 - Jan 2022

- Built a front-end application for minting and staking using React and Web3.js.
- Contributed to staking contracts with Solidity.
- Performed smart contract security audits.

Technologies: DApps, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum

#### SENIOR BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Cybertime.Finance Jan 2021 - Jul 2021

- Designed and developed smart contracts for an upgradeable NFT platform.
- Developed token, staking, voting and aution contracts with ERC20, ERC721, ERC1155 token standards
- Fixed security issues and audited
- Performed smart contract security audits.

Technologies: DApps, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum, Hardhat, Solidity, ERC20, ERC721, ERC1155

## **BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER**

Gembites Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

- Created Several Games Contract (Gambling games) using ERC standards which work on Ethereum and Polygon Networks and deployed those contracts by verification.
- Implemented Metamask, Torus, other wallets to increase user experiences.
- Integrated Chainlink VRF for generating game random number with batching system so that users can play fair and verifiable game easily and fast.
- Built Staking Rewards Contract (ULP), so investors earn GBTS tokens by staking NFTs and LP tokens.
- Developed Dice roll, RPS games.

Technologies: DApps, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum, Chainlink

#### **BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER**

Bitus Labs Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

- Designed the architecture for an auction-based decentralized exchange.
- Analyzed complexity and costs for different approaches for on-chain order matching/execution.
- Supervised and reviewed smart contract development.
- Assisted with back-end and front-end blockchain integration.
- Wrote smart contracts and fixed security holes.
- Developed smart contracts for testing new blockchain features.

Technologies:, Solidity, Remix IDE, Hardhat, Blockchain Platforms, Ethereum, Java

## **FULLSTACK ENGINEER**

Holidu Feb 2016 - Dec 2018

- Developed reusable functional components to onboard users on a financial app for loans and banking, using React, Antd, Hooks, and TypeScript.
- Converted Figma designs to fully functioning pages as the face of the product. Implemented routing using Next.js.
- Implement the designs in Figma using Storybook to confirm implementation.
- Built an iOS and Android mobile app using React Native.
- Developed the back-end (MongoDB, Node.js) and the front-end (Next js, AngularJS) features.
- Implemented the the CI system, optimization of the code, and the testing of the framework for the front-end and back-end.

Technologies: React, TypeScript, Next.js, Vue.js, Nuxt.js, AngularJS, REST, Redux, SCSS, Tailwind CSS, Storybook, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor's degree of Computer Science Nara Institute of Science and Technology Apr 2010 - Oct 2014

# **LANGUAGES**

**ENGLISH**